Guide to the John T. Davis Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2010-133
  - Oversized SXSW Materials
    - "SXSW" (2 folders), 1995 (Box 1940, Folder 1-2)
    - "SXSW" (2 folders), 1997 (Box 1940, Folder 3-4)
    - "SXSW", 1998 (Box 1940, Folder 5)
    - "SXSW", 2000 (Box 1940, Folder 6)
    - "SXSW" (2 folders), 2002 (Box 1941, Folder 1-2)
    - "SXSW" (2 folders), 2006 (Box 1941, Folder 3-4)
    - XL-XTRA Issues, March 15, 2008 (Box 1941, Folder 5)
    - "SXSW", 2009 (Box 1941, Folder 6)
    - "SXSW - Shenandoah", 2010 (Box 1941, Folder 7)
    - "SXSW" (2 folders), 2004 (Box 1942, Folder 1-2)
    - "SXSW" (2 folders), 2007 (Box 1942, Folder 3-4)
    - "SXSW", 2008 (Box 1942, Folder 5)
    - "SXSW" (2 folders), 2005 (Box 1943, Folder 1-2)
    - Other SXSW Articles (2 folders) (Box 1943, Folder 3-4)
    - Other SXSW Articles, 2003 (Box 1943, Folder 5)
    - Other SXSW Articles and Flyers (Box 1943, Folder 6)
    - "SXSW", 2001 (Box 1944, Folder 1)
    - "ACL Fest", 2004 (Box 1944, Folder 2)
    - "ACL Fest", 2006 (Box 1944, Folder 3)
    - "ACL Fest", 2010 (Box 1944, Folder 4)
    - "ACL Fest", 2011 (Box 1944, Folder 5)
    - Other Materials (Box 1944, Folder 6)
    - Season Articles in Austin American Statesmen, 2007 (Box 1944, Folder 7)
  - Oversized "General Articles"
    - XL-ENT Issues, January 4, 2007 (Box 1944, Folder 8)
    - "Remembering Clifford Antone" Article (Box 1944, Folder 9)
    - Willie Nelson 75th Birthday Celebration Article (Box 1944, Folder 10)
- Accession 2019-046
  Additions to the John T. Davis Accessions include his extensive subject files, arranged alphabetically by artist. Contents vary, but typically include promotional photographs, Davis' writings and interview notes, press releases, newspaper clippings, and other ephemera. Not everything in the folders is listed below, but when they exist, photos, interviews, and select items are noted. Folders titles are Davis'.
  - Ace in the Hole Band – 1 photograph (Box 2967, Folder 1)
  - Accordions – Santiago Jimenez; Ponty Bone (including handwritten note) (Box 2967, Folder 2)
  - Albert, Christine – 10 photographs, 1 slide, handwritten note (Box 2967, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Bukka – interview notes, 2007 (Box 2967, Folder 4)
  - Amran, David – 7 photographs; handwritten note (Box 2967, Folder 5)
  - Andrews, Jake (Box 2967, Folder 6)
  - Antone's Nightclub – memorial program for Clifford Antone, 2006 (Box 2967, Folder 7)
  - Antone's Women Performers – Marcia Ball, Lou Ann Barton, Angela Strehli (Box 2967, Folder 8)
  - Antone's Records – 3 photographs: Blues Greats, Barbara Lynn, Angela Strehli; 1991 holiday card with a signed photo of artists (Box 2967, Folder 9)
  - Aquafest (Box 2967, Folder 10)
  - Arc Angels (Box 2967, Folder 11)
  - Armadillo World Headquarters – 7 photographs: Marcia Ball, Commander Cody, The Geezinslaws, Maria Muldaur, Leon Russell, Tracy Nelson, New Riders of the Purple Sage (Box 2967, Folder 12)
  - Ashlock, Jesse (Bob Wills) – 1 photograph (Box 2967, Folder 13)
  - Asylum Street Spankers (Box 2967, Folder 14)
  - Austin, Alternative (Box 2967, Folder 15)
  - Austin, Blues (Box 2967, Folder 16)
  - Austin Blues Tree (Box 2967, Folder 17)
  - Austin City Limits, 2010 season – Lyle Lovett program, ticket, set list; other programs and artist information (Box 2967, Folder 18)
  - Austin, City and Music (Box 2967, Folder 19)
  - Austin, Clubs (Box 2967, Folder 20)
  - Austin, Country (Box 2967, Folder 21)
  - Austin, Gay Rock (Box 2967, Folder 22)
  - Austin, Gospel (Box 2967, Folder 23)
  - Austin, Grammys (Box 2967, Folder 24)
  - Austin, Guitars (Box 2967, Folder 25)
  - Austin, Harps (Box 2967, Folder 26)
  - Austin, Hispanic (Box 2967, Folder 27)
  - Austin, Holidays (Box 2967, Folder 28)
  - Austin, Indie Rock (Box 2967, Folder 29)
  - Austin, Jazz (Box 2967, Folder 30)
  - Austin, Labels (Box 2967, Folder 31)
  - Austin, Metal – "Gray Matter," vol. 1, April 1987 (Box 2967, Folder 32)
  - Austin Music Awards (2 folders) (Box 2967, Folder 33-34)
  - Austin, Music Business (Box 2967, Folder 35)
  - Austin, Music General (Box 2968, Folder 1)
  - Austin, Music History (Box 2968, Folder 2)
  - Austin Lounge Lizards – 4 photographs (Box 2968, Folder 3)
  - "Austin Music: Into the Future" – first report of the Austin Music Advisory Committee, circa 1984 (Box 2968, Folder 4)
  - Austin Music Memorial (Box 2968, Folder 5)
  - Austin Music Video (Box 2968, Folder 6)
  - Austin, Neighborhoods (Box 2968, Folder 7)
  - Austin Opera House (Box 2968, Folder 8)
  - Austin, Punk – 2 photographs: Ty Gavin, Wild Seeds (Box 2968, Folder 9)
  - Austin, Radio (Box 2968, Folder 10)
  - Austin, Rap (Box 2968, Folder 11)
  - Austin, Rave (Box 2968, Folder 12)
  - Austin, Reggae (Box 2968, Folder 13)
  - Austin Rodeo (Box 2968, Folder 14)
  - Austin, Sidemen (Box 2968, Folder 15)
  - Austin, Singer-songwriters – "Songwriters on the Road" program, 1 photograph of David Halley, Jimmy LaFave, Jo Carol Pierce, and Michael Fracasso (Box 2968, Folder 16)
  - Austin, Studios (Box 2968, Folder 17)
  - Austin, Swing (Box 2968, Folder 18)
  - Backyard / T. O'Connor (Box 2968, Folder 19)
  - Ball, David – 5 photographs (1 split ACL with Gary P. Nunn) (Box 2968, Folder 20)
  - Band of Heathens (Box 2968, Folder 21)
  - Barton, Lou Ann – 4 photographs (Box 2968, Folder 22)
  - Bell, T.D. and The Cadillacs (Box 2968, Folder 23)
  - Bell, Vince – 4 photographs (Box 2968, Folder 24)
  - Beto and the Fairlanes (Box 2968, Folder 25)
  - Bettysoo – handwritten note, 2007 (Box 2968, Folder 26)
  - Bland, Bobby (Box 2968, Folder 27)
  - Bollin, Zuzu – 1 photograph (Box 2968, Folder 28)
  - Bone, Ponty (Box 2968, Folder 29)
  - Bongo Joe (Box 2968, Folder 30)
  - Booker, James – 1 photograph (Box 2968, Folder 31)
  - Bramhall, Doyle – 1 photograph (Box 2968, Folder 32)
  - Brammer, Billy Lee (author) (Box 2968, Folder 33)
  - Brave Combo – 4 photographs (Box 2968, Folder 34)
  - Brickell, Edie and New Bohemians – 1 photograph (Box 2968, Folder 35)
  - Broken Spoke (Box 2968, Folder 36)
  - Brotherton, Rich (Box 2968, Folder 37)
  - Brown, Gatemouth (Box 2968, Folder 38)
  - Brown, Junior – 4 photographs, 1 slide, "Big Red" album release promo (Box 2968, Folder 39)
  - Brown, Mel (Box 2968, Folder 40)
  - Brown, Sarah (Box 2968, Folder 41)
  - Burton, Charlie (Box 2968, Folder 42)
  - Bush, Johnnie – 1 photograph (Box 2968, Folder 43)
  - Butthole Surfers (Box 2968, Folder 44)
  - Cactus Café – calendar, February 2004 (Box 2968, Folder 45)
  - Carll, Hayes (Box 2968, Folder 46)
  - Carnaval Brasileiro (Box 2968, Folder 47)
  - Carrasco, Joe "King" – 7 photographs (Box 1927, Folder 48)
  - Carter, Bill – 4 photographs; interview notes, 1990 (Box 1927, Folder 49)
  - Cashdollar, Cindy – interview notes, 2004 (Box 2968, Folder 50)
  - Chaparral – interview notes with Jeff Hughes; Continental Club bar napkin, May 14, 1997 (Box 2968, Folder 51)
  - Chavis, Boozoo – 2 photographs (Box 2968, Folder 52)
  - Chavis, Boozoo – 2 photographs (Box 2968, Folder 53)
  - Choffel, Suzanna (Box 2968, Folder 54)
  - Clark, Gary Jr. (Box 2969, Folder 1)
  - Clark, Glen – 2 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Guy – 4 photographs; interview notes, 1995 (Box 2969, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Jubal (Box 2969, Folder 4)
  - Clark, W.C. – 1 photograph; interview notes, 1989 (Box 2969, Folder 5)
  - Cleaves, Slaid – 10 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 6)
  - Coke, Alex (Box 2969, Folder 7)
  - Collins, Albert (Box 2969, Folder 8)
  - Colvin, Shawn – 8 photographs; 4 slides (2 folders) (Box 2969, Folder 9-10)
  - Conjunto (Box 2969, Folder 11)
  - Continental Club (Box 2969, Folder 12)
  - Cooley, Spade (Box 2969, Folder 13)
  - Copeland, Johnny (Box 2969, Folder 14)
  - Cotton, James – 2 photographs; press packet, 1986 (Box 2969, Folder 15)
  - Court Yard Hounds – interview notes with Emily Robinson, Marty Maguire, and Lloyd Maines, 2013 (Box 2969, Folder 16)
  - Cross Canadian Ragweed – 1 photograph (Box 2969, Folder 17)
  - Crow, Alvin – 3 photographs; interview notes, 1992 (Box 2969, Folder 18)
  - Crowley, Kacy – 1 photograph (Box 2969, Folder 19)
  - Cutrofello, Mary – 5 photographs; 2handwritten notes, undated, 1992 (Box 2969, Folder 20)
  - Dallas Blues (Box 2969, Folder 21)
  - Damnations, TX – 1 photograph (Box 2969, Folder 22)
  - Damron, Allen – 11 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 23)
  - Dawson, Ronnie – 1 photograph (Box 2969, Folder 24)
  - Day, Jimmy (Box 2969, Folder 25)
  - Dayton, Jesse – 2 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 26)
  - Delafose, Geno – 2 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 27)
  - Delafose, John and Eunice Playboys (Box 2969, Folder 28)
  - Derailers – 4 photographs; postcard from Tony Villanueva; "Guide to Style, 1996 (Box 2969, Folder 29)
  - Destiny's Child – 2 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 30)
  - Dixie Chicks – 7 photographs; 2 early press folders; pop-up promo card; "Chick Chat" newsletter (2 folders) (Box 2969, Folder 31-32)
  - Doctor's Mob (Box 2969, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Hepcat (Box 2969, Folder 34)
  - Dr. John – 1 photograph (Box 2969, Folder 35)
  - Duarte, Chris (Box 2969, Folder 36)
  - Dunn, Charlie (bootmaker) (Box 2969, Folder 37)
  - Ealey, Robert (Box 2969, Folder 38)
  - Earle, Stacey – 1 photograph (Box 2969, Folder 39)
  - Earle, Steve – 4 photographs; 1 slide (Box 2969, Folder 40)
  - Eckhardt, Nadine (publicist) (Box 2969, Folder 41)
  - Ed Hall (Box 2969, Folder 42)
  - Edmonson, Kat (Box 2969, Folder 43)
  - Egge, Ana – 2 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 44)
  - 8 ½ Souvenirs (Box 2969, Folder 45)
  - Ely, Joe – 4 photographs (Box 2969, Folder 46)
  - emmajoe's (club) – 1982 calendar listing Ponty Bone, Lisa Gilkyson, Angela Strehli, Butch Hancock, Lucinda Williams, Jimmie Dale Gilmore, Ray Wylie Hubbard, Nanci Griffith, Townes Van Zandt, and others (Box 2969, Folder 47)
  - Erickson, Roky (Box 2969, Folder 48)
  - Escovedo, Alejandro (Box 2969, Folder 49)
  - Fabulous Thunderbirds – 7 photographs (Box 2970, Folder 1)
  - Fastball (Box 2970, Folder 2)
  - Fender, Freddy – 1 photograph (Box 2970, Folder 3)
  - Foley, Blaze – 1 photograph; interview notes with Casey Monahans, Gurf Morlix, Lost John Casner, 1999 (Box 2970, Folder 4)
  - Foley, Sue – 8 photographs (Box 2970, Folder 5)
  - Forsythe, Guy – 3 photographs; interview notes, 1999 (Box 2970, Folder 6)
  - Foster, Radney – 5 photographs (Box 2970, Folder 7)
  - Foster, Ruthie – 1 photograph (Box 2970, Folder 8)
  - Fowler, Kevin (Box 2970, Folder 9)
  - Fracasso, Michael – interview notes, 1995 (Box 2970, Folder 10)
  - Fran, Carol and Clarence Hollimon (Box 2970, Folder 11)
  - Freeman, Denny (Box 2970, Folder 12)
  - Friedman, Kinky – 4 photographs; interview notes, 1993, 1999 (Box 2970, Folder 13)
  - Fromholz, Steven – 10 photographs; interview notes, 1992 (Box 2970, Folder 14)
  - Garza, David – 2 photograph; interview notes, 1992 (Box 2970, Folder 15)
  - Gauthier, Mary (Box 2970, Folder 16)
  - Geezinslaw Brothers / Sammy Allred – 4 photographs; handwritten note, 1983 (Box 2970, Folder 17)
  - Gilkyson, Eliza – 10 photographs; 2018 interview notes; 11 x 17 broadside for 1985 Cactus Café (Box 2970, Folder 18)
  - Gilley's (Club) – 1 photograph of Mickey Gilley (Box 2970, Folder 19)
  - Gilmore, Colin – 1 photograph (Box 2970, Folder 20)
  - Gimble, Johnny – interview notes, 1992 (Box 2970, Folder 21)
  - Glass Eye – 3 photographs; "Glitch News" vol. 4, no. 4, April 1988; 11 x 17 broadside for "Hello Young Lovers" (Box 2970, Folder 22)
  - Gourds (Box 2970, Folder 23)
  - Graham, John Dee (Box 2970, Folder 24)
  - Greater Tuna (Box 2970, Folder 25)
  - Green, Pat – 1 photograph (Box 2970, Folder 26)
  - Greencards – 5 photographs (Box 2970, Folder 27)
  - Greezy Wheels (Box 2970, Folder 28)
  - Grey Ghost (Box 2970, Folder 29)
  - Griffin, Patty – interview notes with Griffin, Emmylou Harris, Julie Miller, Buddy Miller, Michael Fracasso, Shawn Colvin, Michael Ramos, Craig Ross, Lloyd Maines for No Depression feature, 2004 (Box 2970, Folder 30)
  - Grissom, David (Box 2970, Folder 31)
  - Groobees – 2 photographs, 1 slide (Box 2970, Folder 32)
  - Gruene Hall (Club) – interview notes with Pat Molak, Mary Jane Nalley, Robert Earl Keen, 1996 (Box 2970, Folder 33)
  - Grupo Fantasma (Box 2970, Folder 34)
  - Guthrie, Woody (Box 2970, Folder 35)
  - Guy, Buddy – 1 photograph (Box 2970, Folder 36)
  - Hackberry Ramblers – 3 photographs (Box 2970, Folder 37)
  - Halley, David – 3 photographs (Box 2970, Folder 38)
  - Hancock, Tommy / Texana Dames – 5 photographs; letters, 1994 (Box 2970, Folder 39)
  - Hancock, Wayne "The Train" – 2 photographs; interview notes, 1997 (Box 2970, Folder 40)
  - Hand, James (Box 2970, Folder 41)
  - Hendrix, Terri – 1 photograph; 3 letters/emails; Wilory Records brochures (Box 2971, Folder 1)
  - Hernandez, Nash – interview notes with Ruben Hernandez, 1999 (Box 2971, Folder 2)
  - Hester, Carolyn – 2 photographs; interview notes, 1997 (Box 2971, Folder 3)
  - Heybale (Box 2971, Folder 4)
  - Hickman, Sara – 4 photographs; personal note; interview notes, 1990, 1994 (Box 2971, Folder 5)
  - Hinojosa, Tish – 10 photographs, 4 slides; 1993, 1994 and 1996 interview notes; 2002 arrest (3 folders) (Box 2971, Folder 6-8)
  - Hokkanen, Erik and Erik Moll – 3 photographs (Box 2971, Folder 9)
  - Holly, Buddy / Crickets (Box 2971, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins, Lightnin' (Box 2971, Folder 11)
  - Hot Club of Cowtown (Box 2971, Folder 12)
  - Hubbard, Ray Wylie – 2 photographs (one with Jerry Jeff Walker) (Box 2971, Folder 13)
  - Hurd, Cornell – 1 photograph (Box 2971, Folder 14)
  - Ingram, Jack – 2 photographs; interview notes, 1997, 2015 (Box 2971, Folder 15)
  - Jane, Ruby – interview notes with Ruby Jane and Ray Benson, 2012 (Box 2971, Folder 16)
  - Jennings, Waylon – 4 photographs; interview notes, 1992 (Box 2971, Folder 17)
  - Jimenez, Flaco – 2 photographs, 1 slide (Box 2971, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Eric (Box 2971, Folder 19)
  - Joplin, Janice (Box 2971, Folder 20)
  - Juke, Guy (artist) (Box 2971, Folder 21)
  - Keller Brothers (Box 1971, Folder 22)
  - Kerrville Folk Festival (4 folders) (Box 2971, Folder 23-26)
  - Ketchum, Hal – 4 photographs; interview notes, 1988, 1992, 1996, 1997 (Box 2971, Folder 27)
  - Keys, Bobby (Box 2971, Folder 28)
  - King, Shelley (Box 2971, Folder 29)
  - Knox, Buddy (Box 2971, Folder 30)
  - Kristofferson, Kris – 2 photographs; 1996 interview notes with Kristofferson; 1993 interview notes with Stephen Bruton (Box 2971, Folder 31)
  - Lafave, Jimmy – 3 photographs (Box 2971, Folder 32)
  - Lambert, Miranda (Box 2971, Folder 33)
  - Lane, Ronnie (Box 2971, Folder 34)
  - Lee, Dino (Box 2971, Folder 35)
  - Legendary Stardust Cowboy – 1 photograph (Box 2971, Folder 36)
  - LeRoi Brothers (Box 2971, Folder 37)
  - Lester, Lazy – 1 photograph (Box 2971, Folder 38)
  - Lewis, Jerry Lee – 1 photograph (Box 2971, Folder 39)
  - Light Crust Dough Boys – 6 photographs (Box 2972, Folder 1)
  - Lipscomb, Mance (Box 2972, Folder 2)
  - Little Joe y la Familia (Box 2972, Folder 3)
  - Livingston, Bob (Box 2972, Folder 4)
  - Locklin, Hank (Box 2972, Folder 5)
  - Lomaz, Alan and John (Box 2972, Folder 6)
  - Loose Diamonds (Box 2972, Folder 7)
  - Los Lonely Boys (Box 2972, Folder 8)
  - Los Pinky's – 1 photograph (Box 2972, Folder 9)
  - Lost Gonzo Band – 3 photographs; 9 photographs from "Benefit of the Doubt," Austin World Headquarters, February 7, 1980 (Box 2972, Folder 10)
  - Ludwick, Robyn – interview notes, 2011 (Box 2972, Folder 11)
  - Lynn, Barbara (Box 2972, Folder 12)
  - McClinton, Delbert (Box 2972, Folder 13)
  - McKay, Kris – 1 photograph; interview notes, 1991 (Box 2972, Folder 14)
  - McLagen, Ian (Box 2972, Folder 15)
  - McMurtry, James – 5 photographs; interview notes; and interview notes with Tish Hinojosa, 1991 (Box 2972, Folder 16)
  - Mack, Lonnie (Box 2972, Folder 17)
  - Maines, Lloyd (Box 2972, Folder 18)
  - Marsh, Tina (Box 2972, Folder 19)
  - Mayes, Pete – 1 photograph (Box 2972, Folder 20)
  - Meaux, Huey (producer) (Box 2972, Folder 21)
  - Mednick, Lisa – interview notes, 2002 (Box 2972, Folder 22)
  - Mercier, Mandy – 4 photographs (3 signed) (Box 2972, Folder 23)
  - Meyers, Augie – handwritten note (Box 2972, Folder 24)
  - Milligan, Malford – 1 photograph; peacock feather; interview notes, 2003 (Box 2972, Folder 25)
  - Miller, Townsend (Box 2972, Folder 26)
  - Montgomery, Monte – 2 photographs (Box 2972, Folder 27)
  - Moore, Abra – 1 photograph (Box 2972, Folder 28)
  - Moore, Alex (Box 2972, Folder 29)
  - Moore, Ian – 3 photographs (Box 2972, Folder 30)
  - Morlix, Gurf (Box 2972, Folder 31)
  - Morrow, Cory (Box 2972, Folder 32)
  - Morton, Jelly Roll (Box 2972, Folder 33)
  - Murphy, Michael Martin (Box 2972, Folder 34)
  - Murphy, Trish – 2 photographs; 11 x 17 broadside for "Crooked Mile" (Box 2972, Folder 35)
  - Navaira, Emilio – 3 photographs (Box 2972, Folder 36)
  - Neely, Bill (Box 2972, Folder 37)
  - Nelson, Beaver (Box 2972, Folder 38)
  - Neville Brothers – 7 photographs (Box 2972, Folder 39)
  - New Orleans (Box 2972, Folder 40)
  - Nicholas, Johnny – 1 photograph; interview notes, 2011 (Box 2972, Folder 41)
  - Nunn, Gary P. – 2 photographs; 1997 and 2004 interview notes; 1982 press packet including a 45RPM of "I Wanna Go Home with the Armadillo" (Box 2972, Folder 42)
  - Old Settlers Music Festival – interview notes with Louis Karp (1998), Randy Collier (2005), Kasey Chambers (2005), Terri Hendrix (c. 2013), Jane Spivey and Scot Marshall (2012) (Box 2972, Folder 43)
  - Omar and the Howlers – 2 photographs (Box 2972, Folder 44)
  - Pariah (Box 2972, Folder 45)
  - Parks, C-Boy (Box 2972, Folder 46)
  - Parnell, Lee Roy – 7 photographs, 3 slides; interview notes, 1993, 1995 (Box 2972, Folder 47)
  - Peña, Mercedes (Box 2972, Folder 48)
  - Perez, Lourdes (Box 2972, Folder 49)
  - Perkins, Pinetop – 2 photograph (Box 2972, Folder 50)
  - Pierce, Jo Carol – interview notes; packet for Bad Girls Upset by the Truth with photo of Pierce and coauthor Robbie Jacks, 1989 (Box 2972, Folder 51)
  - Pike, Patrice / Little Sister (Box 2972, Folder 52)
  - Pipkin, Turk (comedian, writer) – 1 photograph; interview notes, 2006 (Box 2972, Folder 53)
  - Polk, James (Box 2972, Folder 54)
  - Price, Maryann (Box 2792, Folder 55)
  - Price, Ray – 2 photographs (Box 2792, Folder 56)
  - Price, Toni – 1 photograph; interview notes, 2010 (Box 2792, Folder 57)
  - Pride, Charley (Box 2973, Folder 1)
  - Pryor, Snooky – 3 photographs (Box 2973, Folder 2)
  - Raitt, Bonnie – 2 photographs, including one stage shot (Box 2973, Folder 3)
  - Ramos, Ruben (Box 2973, Folder 4)
  - Ramsey, Willis Alan (Box 2973, Folder 5)
  - Ray, Paul (Box 2973, Folder 6)
  - Rebirth Brass Band (Box 2973, Folder 7)
  - Reckless Kelly – 4 photographs; interview notes (2 folders), 2000, 2006, 2013 (Box 2973, Folder 8-9)
  - Reese, Pauline – 1 photograph (Box 2973, Folder 10)
  - Reid, Ace (cartoonist) (Box 2973, Folder 11)
  - Reno, Johnny – 1 photograph (Box 2973, Folder 12)
  - Rhodes, Kimmie – 6 photographs, 1 slide; handwritten notes; nterview notes; 2003 interview notes with Sharon Ely, 1996, 200, 2003 (Box 2973, Folder 13)
  - Ritter, Tex (Box 2973, Folder 14)
  - Riverfest, 1989 (Box 2973, Folder 15)
  - Robison, Bruce – 6 photographs; 1995, 1999, 2005 interview notes; 2006 interview notes with Kelly Willis (2 folders) (Box 2973, Folder 16-17)
  - Robison, Charlie – 5 photographs; interview notes, 1995, 2006 (Box 2973, Folder 18)
  - Rodgers, Jimmie (Box 2973, Folder 19)
  - Roddy, Ted (Box 2973, Folder 20)
  - Rodriguez, Johnny – 6 photographs; interview notes, 1995 (Box 2973, Folder 21)
  - Royal, Darrell K. (UT football coach) – memorial program; interview notes with son Mack Royal, 2012 (Box 2973, Folder 22)
  - Russell, Calvin – 1 photographs of The Characters (Box 2973, Folder 23)
  - Russell, Shake – 1 photograph with Jack Saunders (Box 2973, Folder 24)
  - Russell, Tom – 2 photographs; handwritten notes; interview notes, 1995, 1997, 1999 (Box 2973, Folder 25)
  - Sahm, Doug – 1 photograph; interviews with Alejandro Escovedo, Bill Bentley, 2009 (Box 2973, Folder 26)
  - Schneider, Doug (Box 2973, Folder 27)
  - Selena – commemorative issue of People magazine, Spring 1995 (Box 2973, Folder 28)
  - Sexton, Charlie (Box 2973, Folder 29)
  - Sexton, Will – 2 photographs; napkin, press pack for The Kill tour, 1986 (Box 2973, Folder 30)
  - Shaver, Billy Joe – 4 photographs, 1 slide; 1993, 2010 interview notes (Box 2973, Folder 31)
  - Shiva's Headband (Box 2973, Folder 32)
  - Shrake, Bud (writer) (Box 2973, Folder 33)
  - Singing Cowboys (Box 2973, Folder 34)
  - Sister 7 – 2 photographs; bumper sticker (Box 2973, Folder 35)
  - Sisters Morales – 5 photographs; handwritten notes (Box 2973, Folder 36)
  - Smith, Darden – 4 photographs; interview notes, 1992 (Box 2973, Folder 37)
  - Smith, Sahara – interview notes, 2010, 2011 (Box 2973, Folder 38)
  - Snider, Todd (Box 2973, Folder 39)
  - Sosa, Mercedes (Box 2973, Folder 40)
  - Soul Hat – 1 photograph (Box 2973, Folder 41)
  - Spoon (Box 2974, Folder 1)
  - Strait, George – 4 photographs including 2 from the film, Pure Country (Box 2974, Folder 2)
  - Strehli, Angela – 3 photographs (1 signed); handwritten notes; interview, 1993 (Box 2974, Folder 3)
  - Sublett, Jesse – 1 photograph of the Skunks at Raul's, by Ken Hoge, 1979 (Box 2974, Folder 4)
  - Sweeney, Sunny (Box 2974, Folder 5)
  - Taylor, Eric (Box 2974, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Chip / Carrie Rodriguez (Box 2974, Folder 7)
  - Taylor, Jesse (Box 2974, Folder 8)
  - Tejano – 3 photographs: Lydia Mendoza, Joel Nava, 1 slide of Nava (Box 2974, Folder 9)
  - Temple, Owen – interview notes, 1999 (Box 2974, Folder 10)
  - Texas Folklife Resources (Box 2974, Folder 11)
  - Texas Music, Misc. (Box 2974, Folder 12)
  - Texas Playboys / Johnny Gimble – 7 photographs (Box 2974, Folder 13)
  - Texas Tornados – 3 photographs; interview notes with Doug Sahm, Augie Meyers, Freddy Fender, 1990 (Box 2974, Folder 14)
  - Thomas, Chris – 5 photographs; interview notes; 11 x 17 broadside, 1990 (Box 2974, Folder 15)
  - Thompson, Hank (Box 2974, Folder 16)
  - Tillman, Floyd (Box 2974, Folder 17)
  - Timbuk 3 – 2 photographs; interview notes, 1990 (Box 2974, Folder 18)
  - Trevino, Rick – 2 photographs (Box 2974, Folder 19)
  - True Believers (Box 2974, Folder 20)
  - Toussaint, Allen – 1 photograph (Box 2974, Folder 21)
  - Tubb, Ernest (Box 2974, Folder 22)
  - Two Tons of Steel (Box 2974, Folder 23)
  - Tyson, Ian – 5 photographs (Box 2974, Folder 24)
  - Uncle Walt's Band: Champ Hood, Walter Hyatt, David Ball – 1 photograph of Walter Hyatt (Box 2974, Folder 25)
  - Vallejo – 1 photograph (Box 2974, Folder 26)
  - Vaughan, Jimmie – 2 photographs (Box 2974, Folder 27)
  - Vaughan, Stevie Ray – 26 photographs including with Mick Jagger, Kim Wilson, Lauren Bacall, Lonnie Mack, Johnny Copeland; laminated invitation to Carnegie Hall party; 1993 memorial program (3 folders) (Box 2974, Folder 28-30)
  - Vonne, Patricia – 2 handwritten notes, postcard (Box 2974, Folder 31)
  - Wagoneers / Monte Warden (Box 2974, Folder 32)
  - Walker, Django – 1 photograph (Box 2974, Folder 33)
  - Walker, T-Bone (Box 2974, Folder 34)
  - Wall, Chris – 1 photograph (Box 2974, Folder 35)
  - Walser, Don – 5 photographs; interview notes; "Dare to Dream" booklet (2 folders), 1994-1996 (Box 2974, Folder 36-37)
  - Watkins, Mitch – 1 photograph (Box 2975, Folder 1)
  - Watson, Dale – 2 photographs; interview notes, 1996, 1998 (Box 2975, Folder 2)
  - Wells, Kitty – 3 photographs; handwritten note from James White, Broken Spoke (Box 2975, Folder 3)
  - Western Swing, General (Box 2975, Folder 4)
  - White, Lavelle – 3 photographs (Box 2975, Folder 5)
  - Wier, Rusty – 1 photograph used on album cover; handwritten note from manager Larry Watkins (Box 2975, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Hank Sr. – 5 photographs re: Mercury Records celebration (Box 2975, Folder 7)